{
    "id": "3ab2b6b2f8624e379cc4775053a38af2",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ………………………… a deep pit.",
            "description": "Dig is an irregular verb. Its past form is dug.",
            "answers": [
                "dug",
                "dugged",
                "digged"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has always been …………………………. towards animals.",
            "description": "Drawn is the past participle form of draw. ",
            "answers": [
                "drawed",
                "drew",
                "drawn"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t drive if you are …………………………….",
            "description": "Drunk is the past participle form of drink. ",
            "answers": [
                "drank",
                "drunk",
                "drinked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We were …………………………….. by the rain.",
            "description": "Driven is the past participle form of drive. ",
            "answers": [
                "driven",
                "drove",
                "drived"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. the cats before I went out.",
            "description": "Fed is the past simple form of feed. ",
            "answers": [
                "feeded",
                "fed",
                "fead"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………… above hills and valleys.",
            "description": "Flew is the past simple form of fly.",
            "answers": [
                "flied",
                "flew",
                "flowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………….. suspicious.",
            "description": "Grew is the past simple form of grow. ",
            "answers": [
                "growed",
                "grew",
                "grown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. the painting on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hanged",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The treasure lay …………………………… for centuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hidden",
                "hided"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was badly ……………………………..",
            "description": "Hurt is the past simple and past participle form of hurt. ",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "hurted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. the mirror against the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leant",
                "leaned",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………………….. the lamp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lit",
                "lighted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}